## **ROBBIE PARR**

With over 7 years Python programming experience, React Native cross platform app development and 3D/VR Game development. Robbie is very motivated to learn new programming languages and frameworks, if he doesn't currently have a skill you want, he'll eagerly retrain and up-skill for you. In the past he has undertaken leadership roles and have encouraged team bonding, which improved team cohesion and performance at stress points in the project/group, making him an invaluable member of any team. After his studies finished, he created a community linking students and industry professionals in York, the Parr-ty Events, hosting several events, a BBQ event and a talk titled "Generative AI and the Future" being highlights. He is looking for his first graduate role.

#### **Education**

University of York	BEng in Computer Science
Third year complete, results pending	2 <sup>nd</sup> Year Average 2:1 Classification

### **Key Technical Skills**

- Strong Programming in Python, Java and Haskell
- Other Programming in C & C++, C#, HTML, CSS, SCSS and JavaScript, R
- App development using React and React Native (With TailwindCSS Styling, Expo Deployment)
- Continuous Integration and Project Management in Git (GitHub)
- Code Architecture in UML
- Databases using Firebase, Sanity and SQLite (Using SQL and XML)
- App Modelling in Balsamiq Wireframes
- Games design using Unity, 3D modelling using Blender
- File storage and forms using Google Drive (Docs, Slides, Sheets, Sites)

#### **Key Transferable skills**

- Leadership
- Responsible
- Punctual
- Organised
- Problem Solving
- Efficient
- Hard-working
- Trustworthy
- Adaptable
- Mathematically Adept

- Scientifically Adept, Especially in Physics
- Technologically Adept
- Diligence
- Dependable
- Discretion
- Perseverance
- Resilience
- Resourceful
- Reliable

#### **Experience**

York Community Consulting	17 <sup>th</sup>	October 2022 - Current
Joined a technology focussed consultancy project as a Senior		Key takeaways
Consultant and upon completion of the project was promoted to a Software Developer in the wider YCC Technology team to continue developing the new YCC website. The website utilises React.JS/Next.Js, SCSS, JSX with a JavaScript backend and firebase data and API endpoints.		<ul> <li>How to build a client facing ReactJS/Next.Js web application.</li> <li>Agile methodologies</li> </ul>

# **ROBBIE PARR**

University of York, Baking Society	18th March 2021 - 24th March 2022, Three University Terms (1 Year, full term)
I was the President of the Baking Society, where I was tasked with organising society events and organising the society as a whole. Hosting events and being the face of the society. For my year long term.	<ul> <li>Key takeaways</li> <li>What it's like to be in a leadership role</li> <li>Importance of good relationships with society members and members of small businesses.</li> </ul>

The Edinburgh Woollen Mill (Horsham Town Centre Branch)		23rd February 2020 - 20th September 2020
Worked as a Sales Assistant for the store.	Key takeaways	
Helping with the selling of goods to	- Customer facing interaction	
customers. Ensuring a excellent customer		
experience.		

Shelton Development Services (Cranleigh)		31 July –	- 4 August 2017
One-week work experience writing	Key takeaway		References
software using Python, Pygame, HTML	- How to work		Head of Software Team /
and CSS to re-create a licence system for	effectively and		Software Architect, Mr
the company's software products.	efficiently as pa	art of a	Fred Trüter: fred@s-d-
	team		s.co.uk